Finding Aid for the Ojai Music Festival Records PASC-M.0277
UCLA Library Special Collections
Ojai Music Festival records
1940-2006
UCLA Library Special Collections
Ojai Music Festival 1940-
PASC-M.0277
73.5 Linear Feet (147 boxes)
The collection consists of materials pertaining to the Ojai Music Festival, founded in 1947. The festival is held annually in Ojai, CA, in Ventura County. Notable conductors and performers have included Pierre Boulez, Aaron Copland, Igor Stravinsky, Michael Tilson Thomas, Dawn Upshaw, the Kronos Quartet and Murray Perahia, among many others. The collection includes programs, artist biographies, press clippings, business records, and recordings. The collection is in the midst of being processed. The finding aid will be updated periodically.
Conditions Governing Access
Portions of collection unprocessed. Material in the Unprocessed Materials series is unavailable for access. Please contact Special Collections reference (spec-coll@library.ucla.edu) for more information.
All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
CONTAINS DIGITAL AND AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: This collection contains both processed and unprocessed digital and audiovisual materials. For information about the access status of the material that you are looking for, refer to the Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note at the series and file levels. All requests to access processed digital materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
The collection was donated by the Ojai Music Festival.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9953261693606533
Administrative/Biographical History
Established in 1947 by music aficionado John Bauer, the Ojai Music Festival has fostered a healthy spirit of eclecticism in its adventurous programs, gaining a worldwide reputation for attracting artists who are given artistic freedom as they perform exceptional pieces of classical music.
That spirit was reinforced in 1954 with the appointment of Lawrence Morton as the Festival Artistic Director. A man of broad musical tastes, Morton was a visionary whose constant curiosity and unwavering integrity shaped the Festival's future direction. Under his leadership, the Ojai Festival developed an enduring concept whereby the artistic director engages a different Festival music director each year around whom that year's Festival is built.
Among the Festival's diverse music directors have been such renowned musical luminaries as composers John Adams, Ingolf Dahl, Peter Maxwell Davies, Lukas Foss, John Harbison and Oliver Knussen; conductors Kent Nagano, Michael Tilson Thomas, and Esa-Pekka Salonen; and instrumentalists Emanuel Ax and Mitsuko Uchida.
In its sixth decade, the Festival - under the leadership of Artistic Director Thomas W. Morris - continues this unparalleled musical legacy in which the creativity of the moment and the artists define each year's event.
The Ojai Music Festival offers educational programs for students attending Ojai Valley public schools, enriching the region's cultural opportunities and promoting classical music to future generations.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of materials pertaining to the Ojai Music Festival, founded in 1947. The festival is held annually in Ojai, CA, in Ventura County. Notable conductors and performers have included Pierre Boulez, Aaron Copland, Igor Stravinsky, Michael Tilson Thomas, Dawn Upshaw, the Kronos Quartet and Murray Perahia, among many others. The collection includes programs, artist biographies, press clippings, business records, and recordings.
Arrangement
The collection is organized into the following series:
Series 1: Festival Recordings and Artist Interviews, 1940s-1980s
Series 2: Artist Biographies and Contracts, 1940s-1980s
Series 3. Business Papers, 1940s-1990s
Series 4. Programs
Series 5. Correspondence
Series 6. Artists
Series 7. Clippings--Individuals--Performers
Series 8. Clippings--Individuals--Composers
Series 9. Clippings--Individuals--Philanthropists
Series 10. Clippings--Groups--Performance ensembles
Series 11. Ojai Clippings, 1940s-1980s
Series 12. Unprocessed Materials
Series 13. Ojai Archives. 1960-1965
Ojai Music Festival 1940- -- Archives
- Festival Recordings and Artist Interviews, 1940s-1980s; Series 1.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  CONTAINS DIGITAL AND AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: This collection contains both processed and unprocessed digital and audiovisual materials. Digital and audiovisual materials are not currently available for access, unless otherwise noted in a Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note at the file levels. All requests to access processed materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
  - [No Title], 1983 June 4; open reel audio tape (Box 15, Folder 2)
    General note
    On item: Program #3, Tape #226, Reel 1 of 3.
  - [No Title], 1983 June 2; open reel audio tape (Box 15, Folder 9)
    On item: Reel, Program #2, no tape #. Reel 3 of 4.
  - [No Title], 1956 December; open reel audio tape (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Back of box has track list 1-13, primarily gamelan pieces. Says reverse side has John Berry, Hindu chants.
  - [No Title], 1983 June 5; open reel audio tape (Box 19, Folder 2)
    On item: Reel 2 of 4; Program #4.
    - Concerto for 2, 2005 June 5; uclapasc0277_019_002; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 00:36:19) 7 inches (Box 19, Case 2)
      CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials are available for access. All requests to access digital materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
      Scope and Contents
      Content note: Program 5; string orch.
  - [No Title], 1983?; open reel audio tape (Box 19, Folder 3)
    On item: Reel 3 of 4; Program #4.
  - [No Title], 1985 June 1; open reel audio tape (Box 66, Folder 10)
    On item: Ojai 8502,Reel 4 of 4.
  - 1979 #1, 1 sound cassette (Box 67, Folder 6)
    Scope and Contents note
    No program list.
    Title from container.
  - 1979 #2, Cassette tape (Box 67, Folder 7)
    No program list
  - 1979 #3, Cassette tape (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - 1982 #1, Cassette tape (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - 1982 #2, Cassette tape (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - 1982 #3, Cassette tape (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - 1982 #4, 1 sound cassette (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - 1982 #5, 1 sound cassette (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - 1983 Ojai Fest, 1983 June 2; open reel audio tape (Box 35, Folder 9)
    Program #1 Ravi Shankar-2nd half-1st raja Reel 2 of 3
    Length: 28:43
  - 1983 Ojai Fest Shankar--2nd Half--2nd raja, 1983 June 2; open reel audio tape (Box 58, Folder 1)
    Reel Program 1 Reel 3 of 3
    Duration: 28:27
  - 627--Ojai Festival, 1981 or 1982?; 1 sound cassette (Box 67, Folder 5)
    Excerpts of works by Brahms, Bartok, and Messiaen.
    No program number or year indicated.
  - 8702 Amb., 1987 May 30; open reel audio tape (Box 66, Folder 15)
    On item: Ojai 8702, Ambience, Tape 469.
  - 8702 Amb. 2, 1987 May 30; open reel audio tape (Box 66, Folder 16)
    On item: Ojai 8702, Ambience #2, Tape 469.
  - 9 DAT Tapes, Digital Audio Tapes (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Numbers: 8701-8705 8901-8905
    Program lists for some of the tapes in the box.
    - Debussy, Boulez, Ravel, uclapasc0277_047_001a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 00:41:26) 7 inches (Box 47, Case 1)
      Transcribed from container: DEBUSSY- Finale from Sonata for flute, viola, and harp; BOULEZ- Eclat/Multiples; RAVEL- Ma Mere 1'Oye
    - Debussy, Boulez, Ravel, uclapasc0277_047_001b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 00:07:44) 7 inches (Box 47, Case 1)
    - Ojai 8704, 1988 April 20; uclapasc0277_047_004; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 00:57:58) 7 inches (Box 47, Case 4)
      Content Note: KUSC: Bach, Morley, Foss, Britten
    - Ojai 8901, undated; uclapasc0277_047_006; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 01:26:00) 7 inches (Box 47, Case 6)
    - Ojai 8902, undated; uclapasc0277_047_007; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 01:08:00) 7 inches (Box 47, Case 7)
    - Ojai 8903, undated; uclapasc0277_047_008; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 01:16:00) 7 inches (Box 47, Case 8)
    - Ojai 8904, undated; uclapasc0277_047_009; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 01:41:00) 7 inches (Box 47, Case 9)
    - Ojai 8905, undated; uclapasc0277_047_010; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 01:19:00) 7 inches (Box 47, Case 10)
  - Alley Amb, 1983 June 5; open reel audio tape (Box 8, Folder 7)
    On item: Program #4, Tape #250.
  - Ambience, 1982; open reel audio tape (Box 57, Folder 7)
    On item: Reel, Ambience,Reel Amb 1.
  - Ambience, 1982 June 4; open reel audio tape (Box 57, Folder 10)
    On item: Ambience, Tape #1, Reel 2 of 2.
  - Ambience 1, 1982; open reel audio tape (Box 57, Folder 3)
    On item: Ojai 82, Tape 2, Ambience 1, Reel: Ambience 1.
  - Ambience 2, 1982; open reel audio tape (Box 57, Folder 5)
    On item: Reel Amb of 2.
  - Ambreuze, 1983 June 5; open reel audio tape (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Beethoven, 1984 June 2; open reel audio tape (Box 66, Folder 6)
    On item: Ojai 8402, Reel 2 of 3. Sticker on all three reels says 8401, but it is actually 8402.
  - Beethoven, 1984 June 2; open reel audio tape (Box 66, Folder 7)
    On item: Ojai 8402, Reel 3 of 3.
  - Boulez, 1984 June 2-November 20; open reel audio tape (Box 66, Folder 5)
    On item: Ojai 8402, Reel 1 of 3.Program, 3 reels, 1: Boulez, 2: Beethoven, 3: Beethoven. Duration: 1:33:40.
  - Carol Wincenc Interview, 1987 May 30; open reel audio tape (Box 63, Folder 6)
    On item: Ojai 87 01/2.
    - Ojai Sample Tape 1982, uclapasc0277_063_006; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 00:22:17) 7 inches (Box 63, Case 6)
  - Conc. for..., 1983 June 5; open reel audio tape (Box 19, Folder 5)
    Title from container. Sticker is torn and half of information is missing. Seems to go with folder 4.
  - Concerto for 2 solo pf, 1982 June 5; open reel audio tape (Box 17, Folder 10)
    On item: Reel 3 of x; Tape #2.
  - Concerto for 2, String Orch, 1983 June 5; open reel audio tape (Box 19, Folder 5)
    On item: Reel 1 of 2; Program #5; tape #226. Title from container.
    - Swanne Alley Segments, 1983 June 5; uclapasc0277_019_005; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 00:24:57) 7 inches (Box 19, Case 5)
      Content note: Program #4, Reel 2 of 4
  - Daniel Lewis Interview, 1983 May 26; open reel audio tape (Box 8, Folder 4)
    On item: Duration: 31 minutes. Tape #250.
  - Daniel Lewis Interview, 1983 May 26; open reel audio tape (Box 55, Folder 11)
    On item: Ojai 1983, 5 minutes, Reel 2 of 2.
    - Program #2 Outz, 1983 August 4; uclapasc0277_055_011; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 00:23:46) 7 inches (Box 55, Case 11)
      Tape # 250
  - Davies Brass, 1987?; open reel audio tape (Box 66, Folder 18)
    On item: Ojai 8703, Reel 1.
  - DiLasso, Notre Dame, Lessuer, Le Vauve [?], 5-31-87; open reel audio tape (Box 66, Folder 11)
    On container, "Program 8704, Tape 469, Reel 1 of 2."
  - Eclat-Multiples, 1984 June 2; open reel audio tape (Box 66, Folder 3)
    On item: Ojai 8401, Reel 3 of 4.
  - En Blanc, 1982 June 5; open reel audio tape (Box 17, Folder 5)
    On item: Reel 4 of 5; Program #2; no tape #.
  - Fantasia, 1982 June 5; open reel audio tape (Box 18, Folder 7)
    On item: Reel 1; no program #; tape #2.
  - Festivals 1972 Concert #3 Selections #1 and #2, open reel audio tape (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Ojai Festival concert no. 3, 1972 May 27; uclapasc0277_063_001a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 00:17:03) 7 inches (Box 63, Case 1)
      Transcribed from container: Michael Zearott, Conductor, Selections #1 & 2; Side 1: Schuller; Side 2: Handel
    - Ojai Festival concert no. 3, 1972 May 27; uclapasc0277_063_001b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 00:19:08) 7 inches (Box 63, Case 1)
      Michael Zearott, Conductor, Selections #1 & 2; Side 1: Schuller; Side 2: Handel
  - Foss Interview & Job #1, 1983?; three 7" open reel audio tapes (Box 63)
    - Lukas Foss Interview/JLB, undated; uclapasc0277_063_005; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 00:15:41) 7 inches (Box 63, Case 5)
      Foss Interview #3; JLB # 1
  - Grosse Fugue, 1982 June 5; open reel audio tape (Box 18, Folder 6)
    On item: Reel 2; no program #; tape #2.
  - Haydn, 6-1-85; 8-29-85; Reel and production list (Box 66, Folder 8)
    8502 Reel 1 of 4
    Program 4 reels 1: Haydn 2: Takamitzu 3: Brahms 4: Brahms, Haydn
  - Henze, 1983 June 4; open reel audio tape (Box 15, Folder 7)
    On item: Reel 1 of 4.
  - Henze, 1983 June 4; open reel audio tape (Box 20, Folder 11)
    On item: Reel 1 of 4; Program #2; tape #250.
  - Kennon, 1983 June 4; open reel audio tape (Box 15, Folder 6)
    On item: Reel, Program #2, Tape #226, Reel 2 of 4. Duration: 23:38
  - Kennon, 1983 June 4; open reel audio tape (Box 20, Folder 12)
    On item: Reel 2 of 4; Program #2; tape #250, Duration: 28:38.
  - Laurence Deutsch Ojai Festival, 5-7-91; Foto-tronics reel NTSC (Box 63, Folder 7)
    46 minutes in length.
    - The Schubertians, 2005 May 28; uclapasc0277_063_007; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 00:22:54) 7 inches (Box 63, Case 7)
      U.S.C. (Santa Barbara); Side 2 only, Side 1 blank
  - Lucas Foss Interview, 1983?; open reel audio tape (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Lukas Foss Interview, undated; uclapasc0277_063_004; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 00:15:52) 7 inches (Box 63, Case 4)
      Foss Interview 2
  - Milhaud, 1983 June 4; open reel audio tape (Box 19, Folder 6)
    On item: Reel 3 of 3; Program #3; Tape 256.
    - Swanne Alley Segments, 2005 June 5; uclapasc0277_019_006; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 00:22:43) 7 inches (Box 19, Case 6)
      Content note: Program #4, Reel 3 of 4
  - Milhavo, 1983 June 4; open reel audio tape (Box 15, Folder 3)
    On item: Program #3, Tape #226.Reel 3 of 3.
  - Mozart & Stravinsky Octet, 1982 June 4; open reel audio tape (Box 17, Folder 7)
    On item: Reel 2 of 4; Tape #1.
  - Music Outs, 1982; open reel audio tape (Box 57, Folder 2)
    On item: Program #2.
  - Music Outs, 1982; open reel audio tape (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Music Outs Ojai #5, 1983; open reel audio tape (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Ojai 83 Outz, 1983 August 4; open reel audio tape (Box 55, Folder 12)
    Ojai 1983 Program 2 Outz no reel number
  - Ojai 83 Program 2, 6-4-83; Reel in styrofoam with plastic (Box 55, Folder 2)
    Ojai 83 Program 2 Tape 250 Reel 1
    - Kennon Dulce, 1983 June 4; uclapasc0277_055_002; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 00:31:24) 7 inches (Box 55, Case 2)
      Program #2, Reel 2
  - Ojai 83 Program 2, 6-4-83; Reel in styrofoam with plastic (Box 55, Folder 3)
    Ojai 83 Program 2 Kennon-Dulce Reel 2
    - Encore II: Blazard, 1983 June 4; uclapasc0277_055_003; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 00:11:29) 7 inches (Box 55, Case 3)
      Program #2, Tape #250, Reel 5
  - Ojai 83 Program 2, 6-4-83; Reel in styrofoam with plastic (Box 55, Folder 4)
    Ojai 83 Program 2 Encore II: Blazard [?] Reel 5
    - Ambience 2, 1983 June 4; uclapasc0277_055_004; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 00:12:56) 7 inches (Box 55, Case 4)
      Program #2
  - Ojai 83 Program 2, 6-4-83; Reel in styrofoam with plastic (Box 55, Folder 5)
    Ojai 83 Program 2 Ambience 2 Reel: amb 2
    - Ambience 1, 1983 June 3; uclapasc0277_055_005; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 00:28:45) 7 inches (Box 55, Case 5)
  - Ojai 83 Program 2, 6-4-83; Reel in styrofoam with plastic (Box 55, Folder 6)
    Ojai 83 Program 2 Ambience 1 Reel: Amb 1
    - R.C.'s Vox Trx Program # 2, 1983 August 3; uclapasc0277_055_006; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 00:21:15) 7 inches (Box 55, Case 6)
      Tape #250, Reel 1
  - Ojai 83 Program 2, 8-3-83; Reel in styrofoam with plastic (Box 55, Folder 7)
    Ojai 83 Program 2 R.C.'s Vox Trx Reel: 1 of x
    - R.C.'s Vox Program # 3, 1983 August 17; uclapasc0277_055_007; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 00:17:13) 7 inches (Box 55, Case 7)
      Tape #250
  - Ojai 83 Program 3, 8-17-83; Reel in styrofoam without plastic (Box 55, Folder 8)
    Ojai 83 Program 2 R.C.'s Vox
    - Program #3 Outs, 2005 June 5; uclapasc0277_055_008; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 00:18:58) 7 inches (Box 55, Case 8)
  - Ojai 83 Program 3, 1983; Reel in styrofoam without plastic (Box 55, Folder 9)
    Ojai 1983 Pgm. #3 Outs
    - Program #3 Ambience, 1983 June 4; uclapasc0277_055_009; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 00:33:08) 7 inches (Box 55, Case 9)
  - Ojai 83 Program 3, 6-4-83; Reel in styrofoam with plastic (Box 55, Folder 10)
    Ojai 1983 Pgm. #3 Ambience Reel: Amb
    - Daniel Lewis Interview, 1983 May 26; uclapasc0277_055_010; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 00:05:03) 7 inches (Box 55, Case 10)
      Reel 2 of 2
  - Ojai '83 Program 5 Vivaldi, June 5, 1983; Sound reel in styrofoam casing (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Reel. Sticker says Tape #250.
  - Ojai 83 Ravi Shankar, 6-2-83; Sound reel in plastic with styrofoam casing (Box 35, Folder 3)
    Reel 2 of x; Program #1; no tape #
  - Ojai 83 Riley & Sullinen [?], 6-4-83; Sound reel in styrofoam casing (Box 17, Folder 1)
    Reel 3 of 4; Program 2; no tape number
  - Ojai 83' S. Alley, 6-5-83; Sound reel in plastic and styrofoam casing (Box 19, Folder 4)
    Reel 4 of 4; Program #4; tape #226
    - Swanne Alley Segments, 1983 June 5; uclapasc0277_019_004; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 00:27:22) 7 inches (Box 19, Case 4)
      Content note: Reel 1 of 4; Program 4
  - Ojai 83 Shankar 2nd half, 6-2-83; Sound reel in plastic with styrofoam casing (Box 35, Folder 4)
    Reel 4 of 4; Program #1; no tape #
  - Ojai 83 Shankar Part 1, 6-2-83; Sound reel in plastic with styrofoam casing (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Ojai 83 Shostakavich: [sic] Qt. #8, 6-4-83; Sound reel in plastic with styrofoam casing (Box 20, Folder 5)
    Reel 4 of 4; Program #2; no tape #
    Length: 30:11
  - Ojai 83 Shuber [sic] Songs, 6-4-83; Sound reel in plastic with styrofoam casing (Box 19, Folder 9)
    Reel 2 of 3; Program #3; tape #250
    - Milhaud, 1983 June 4; uclapasc0277_019_009; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 00:30:16) 7 inches (Box 19, Case 9)
      Content note: Program #3, Tape 250, Reel 3 of 3
  - Ojai 83 Stravinsky, 6-4-83; Sound reel in plastic with styrofoam casing (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Reel 1 of 3; Program #3; tape #250
  - Ojai 83 Swan Alley Seg [sic], 6-5-83; Sound reel in plastic with styrofoam casing (Box 20, Folder 6)
    Reel 2 of 4; Program #4; tape #250
  - Ojai '83 Swan Alley/Dowland, 6-5-83; Sound reel in plastic with styrofoam casing (Box 20, Folder 7)
    Reel 3 of 4; Program #4; tape #250
  - Ojai '83 Swan Alley/Final, 6-5-83; Sound reel in plastic with styrofoam casing (Box 20, Folder 8)
    Reel 4 of 4; Program #4; tape #250
  - Ojai 83' Swanne Alley SBG, 6-5-83; Sound reel in plastic and styrofoam casing (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Reel 1 of 4; Program #4; no tape #
    - Concerto for 2, 2005 June 5; uclapasc0277_019_001; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:35:34) 7 inches (Box 19, Case 1)
      Content note: Program 5; string orch. Reel 1 of 2
  - Ojai 8403 Reel 1 of 4, 6-3-84; 9-6-84; Reel in plastic, on plastic spool in box; production notes (Box 68, Folder 15)
    Production notes: 4 reels Reel 1: Berg, Lyric Suite Reel 2: Webern, Symphony op. 21; Boulez, Messagesquisses Reel 3: Bartok, Two Rhapsodies for Violin & Orch. Reel 4: Ravel, Mother Goose Suite Total: 1:43:54
  - Ojai 8403 Reel 2 of 4, 6-3-84; Reel in plastic, on plastic spool in box (Box 68, Folder 16)
    Reel 2 of 4 Webern, Boulez
  - Ojai 8403 Reel 3 of 4, 6-3-84; Reel in plastic, on plastic spool in box (Box 68, Folder 17)
    Reel 3 of 4 Bartok
  - Ojai 8403 Reel 4 of 4, 6-3-84; Reel in plastic, on plastic spool in box (Box 68, Folder 18)
    Reel 3 of 4 Ravel
  - Ojai 8501, 1985; one sound reel (Box 96, Folder 3)
    Ojai '85, program 4 Ives Reel 4 of 4 Stereo, master, dolby
    Reel labeled KUSC FM.
  - Ojai 8501, 5-31-85; Sound reel in plastic; no styrofoam (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Reel 2 of 5; Program #8501; no tape #
  - Ojai 8501, 5-31-85; Sound reel in plastic; no styrofoam (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Reel 5 of 5; Program #8501; no tape #
  - Ojai 8501, 5-31-85; Sound reel in plastic; no styrofoam (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Reel 4 of 5; Program #8501; no tape #
  - Ojai 8501, 5-31-85; Sound reel in plastic; no styrofoam (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Reel 3 of 5; Program #8501; no tape #
  - Ojai 8501 Chopin, Debussy, 5-31-85, 8-30-85; Sound reel in plastic; no styrofoam; plus KUSC memo (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Reel 1 of 5; Program #8501; Tape #469
    Memo from Ted. Ojai 8501 5 reels. Reel 1: Chopin- Barcarolle; Debussy- Two Preludes from Book two Reel 2: Albeniz- Two pieces from Iberia Reel 3: Messiaen- Vingt Regards (excerpts 1-5) Reel 4: Messiaen- Vingt Regards (excerpts 6-9) Reel 5: Messiaen- Vingt Regards (excerpt 10) Total time: 1:57:32
  - Ojai 8501 Reel 1 of 4, 1985; Reel on metal spool in box; production list (Box 68, Folder 20)
    Production info: 4 reels 1: Schubert, Songs 2: Messiaen, Chants de Terre et de Ciel 3: Tchaikovsky, Songs 1-7 4: Ives, Songs Total: 1:52:48
  - Ojai 8503 Messaien, 6-1-85; Reel (Box 66, Folder 13)
    Reel 3 of 4
    Reels 1 and 2 of this series not in this box.
  - Ojai 8503 Messiaen, 6-1-85; reel (Box 66, Folder 14)
    Reel 4 of 4
  - Ojai 8504, 1985; one sound reel (Box 96, Folder 4)
    Ojai '85, Program 4 Reel 3 of 4 Tchaikovksy Master, stereo, dolby
    Labeled KUSC FM
  - Ojai 8504 2 of 4, 1985; Reel (Box 58, Folder 6)
    Reel Program 8504 Messiaen Reel 2 of 4
  - Ojai 8505 1 of 4 Bartok, 6-2-85; Sound reel in cardboard box (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Reel, Program #8505, Tape #469. 1 of 4.
    Sheet from KUSC has memo from Ted. 9-17-85. Program: Bartok-Three Village Sceens [sic]; Mozart: Symphony #28 in C, K200; Messiaen-Trois Petits Liturgies. All four reels together are 1:34:12 in length.
  - Ojai 8505 2 of 4 Mozart, 6-2-85; Sound reel in cardboard box (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Reel, Program #8505, Tape #469. 2 of 4.
  - Ojai 8505 3 of 4 Messiaen, 6-2-85; Sound reel in cardboard box (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Reel, Program #8505, Tape #469.
    Says Reel 3 of 4.
  - Ojai 8505 Reel 4 of 4, 6-3-84; Reel on metal spool in box (Box 68, Folder 19)
    Reel 4 of 4 Messiaen
  - Ojai 8604, 6-1-86; Sound reel in cardboard box (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Reel 2, Program #8704, Tape #469.
    Hard to read sticker. Might say: SC Halbern, Kurog Duets. Check against program.
  - Ojai 8701 Reel 1 of 2, 05-29-87; Reel on metal spool in box (Box 68, Folder 6)
    8701 Tape 469 Purcell Reel 1 of 2
  - Ojai 8701 Reel 2 of 2, 05-29-87; Reel on metal spool in box (Box 68, Folder 7)
    8701 Tape 469 Knussen/Foss Reel 2 of 2
  - Ojai 8702 1 of 2, May 30, 1987; one sound reel (Box 96, Folder 1)
    Program #8702 Messiaen, Couperin, Hill Master, stereo, dolby
  - Ojai 8702 Little set, 5-30-87; Reel (Box 66, Folder 17)
    Ojai 8702 Tape 469 Reel 4
    Other reels from this program not in this box
  - Ojai 8702 Reel 1 of 2, 05-30-87; Reel on metal spool in box (Box 68, Folder 8)
    8702 Reel 1 of 2 Bach/Wuorinen
  - Ojai 8702 Reel 2 of 2, 05-29-87; Reel on metal spool in box (Box 68, Folder 9)
    8702 Reel 2 of 2 Handel
  - Ojai 8702 Reel 2 of 2, 05-30-87; Reel on spool; no plastic (Box 68, Folder 10)
    Duplicate of other reel?
  - Ojai 8703, May 30, 1987; one sound reel (Box 96, Folder 2)